Are you done? Where's Yeon-su?
We didn't know it would
suddenly rain so much.
I just came to get these.
Ms. Kook is still on standby.
I see.
We should just call it a day.
It's pouring.
I'll go get Ms. Kook then.
She probably doesn't have an umbrella.
I'll go.
What is it?
Did you decide to shoot this
because of Ms. Kook?
Where's Yeon-su?
Why is it raining so much?
I hate it when things
don't go according to plan.
Where should we shoot the rest?
Anything I can't control
is just a risk.
Back then and even now,
Yeon-su is someone like that to me.
The first time I saw Yeon-su…
No, that's not important.
It doesn't matter who liked her first.
I was the jerk
who liked his friend's girlfriend.
So I had to keep making plans…
in order to not cross any lines.
Hey, Yeon-su and I are going to eat
at our restaurant. Join us.
I didn't want to be someone
who would childishly teeter
between friendship and love.
I'm busy.
What do you mean?
You're reading a comic book.
I just finished.
I have a report to write.
Hey, I get that Yeon-su is kind of weird.
But you're being so obvious
that you don't like her.
She's my girlfriend.
It's nothing like that.
But why do I feel like
you're avoiding her?
I'm not.
Stop the nonsense and just go.
She'll yell at you for being late. Go.
At first, it was hard.
By the way,
you're weirder than she is.
But I got used to it after a while.
My plan was simple.
Ji-ung, can you give me a ride…
Don't get involved
in any coincidental encounters.
Darn it.
We broke up.
Don't get fooled by words like that.
Just go and apologize.
Should we try out
the new teokbokki place today?
- It seems pretty good.
- Okay.
Try to meet new people.
It looks as if it's over
for real this time, right?
KOOK YEON-SU
DELETE, SYNC CONTACT, SHARE CONTACT
I promised myself not to be shaken
no matter what happened.
Yeon-su!
And…
to slowly forget her.
But just when I had thought
that my plan had succeeded…
How have you been, Ji-ung?
…Yeon-su appeared in front of me again.
As a risk that's out of my control.
Just like now.
But…
now I'm thinking,
if things won't go according to plan,
do I even need a plan anymore?
EPISODE 9
JUST FRIENDS
Ung! I called you so many times!
You're still sleeping?
Ung.
Ung?
Are you okay?
Oh, gosh.
Get up.
You're burning up!
Are you okay?
CULTURE-COMPLEX, BEAUTY, FASHION
Thanks to our past projects,
we have a lot of marketing requests
for culture-complex centers.
The ones we can work on…
Ms. Kook.
Ms. Kook!
Oh, right.
Are you okay?
Are you not feeling well?
You look a bit pale.
You should have gotten more rest.
Are you really okay?
I'm sorry. Let's take a short break.
All right.
She's been like that for days.
Five days to be exact.
She's been out of it
since she came back from her leave.
Did something happen?
What's wrong with me?
This isn't right.
SOL-I
- Yes?
- What?
It's not like you to answer right away.
What's up?
Come over after work.
I have a new dish.
Next time. I'm busy.
Again? But your last project just ended.
I need to test out my dish.
Call someone else.
Why don't you try calling Gu Eun-ho?
He's trying it right now.
But he says everything tastes bad.
I can't trust him.
What?
Why's he over there? Isn't he working?
Is he not busy?
- Hey, aren't you busy?
- No.
Why are you always free?
Don't you have work?
It seems like he's unemployed.
He's resting since Ung's taking a break.
He's taking a break?
Anyway, come over after you get off work.
What is Ung thinking?
How long have I been like this?
Mom.
Mom!
You're up.
Come here.
Let me see if your fever's down.
Your fever's all gone.
You get a bad fever when you catch a cold.
Have you been taking the medicine
I sent you last time?
- Yes.
- Really?
You only took some and stopped, right?
I heard you got drenched
in the rain during the trip.
I should rip Eun-ho's mouth out.
But what were you doing here?
I think this is the first time
seeing your drawings
up close like this.
You left early when I drew at that event.
When did my son grow up so much?
What?
I've been a grown man for quite a while.
Why did you grow up all alone?
It must have been difficult for you.
Don't try to carry
all the burden yourself.
You don't have to.
I guess me and Dad
are still quite lacking
for you to depend on us.
It's not that, so don't worry.
I'm just more comfortable alone.
Ung, but still…
Mom, it's okay.
I like the way things are right now.
It's okay to be alone from the start.
You'd be used to it.
But being alone after being with someone
isn't something
I want to experience again.
We just had instant noodles
for lunch the first day.
And we grilled meat
and made stew for dinner.
One of them was a really good cook.
And then the next day…
What did we have again?
Right, the cast slept in,
so the rest of us ate out.
And then for lunch--
Hey, I wasn't asking what you ate there.
I see.
Ji-ung filmed Ms. Kook on the first day,
and Chae-ran filmed Mr. Choi.
I stayed back and set up the lights.
And we filmed at the house in the evening.
- And then--
- No, not that.
Didn't anything interesting happen?
Right. The casts' friends were really fun.
They showed me around the village.
Hey. Eat up.
Drink up.
Just shut up and drink.
Jeez.
Oh, right.
There was heavy rain all of a sudden
so we had to stop filming for a whole day.
And?
Chae-ran was with Ms. Kook,
but she came back alone.
And then Ji-ung arrived
with Ms. Kook a while later.
And Mr. Choi was gone for a long time
then came back all drenched.
Is that so?
So what happened?
We canceled the shoot.
We were going to film more the next day,
but we couldn't because the cast
went back to Seoul in the morning.
I see…
But why didn't you tell me earlier?
You should have told me
when I asked if anything happened!
But why did the cast leave so early?
Well, it seemed like urgent business.
But it did seem like
something was going on.
It felt like the cast might have fought…
No, it felt different than a fight.
But what's even more strange
is that Ji-ung and Chae-ran
were acting weird too.
They were quiet.
- Why?
- Well…
I'm not sure why.
But the two of them went out to talk
that night for a long time.
Just the two of them?
Really? Is that so?
Ji-ung, I ordered dinner.
Come and have some later.
Did you get off work?
Did you have dinner yet?
Did you get a good…
I want to make it seem like
nothing's happened between us, but…
KIM JI-UNG
Where are you? Give me the address.
Are you coming for me?
I can find you easily. Delete the video.
I'm the producer.
Not if you end up dead. Delete it.
You make that face all the time anyway.
That's the best I can get out of you.
It's the producer that's the problem.
LEEZAKAYA
Fine, I'll delete it.
Did you have dinner?
WITH UNG
- You're back.
- Hey.
How is he? Is his fever down?
Yes.
His fever's down,
and I gave him some food.
- But why do you look so down?
- What?
- Is he not feeling well?
- It's not that.
I looked around his studio,
and it seemed
he still has trouble sleeping.
He has a lot more pills now.
He must be spending all his time there.
When I looked around,
it seemed so lonely there.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Do you think he will be okay like this?
Ung isn't that weak.
He'll be all right.
UNG'S DRAWINGS ORGANIZED BY EUN-HO
DRAWINGS FROM UNG'S DARK TIMES
I like that you're an amazing artist
but I hope you never experience
this phase again.
- Did you sleep with him?
- Are you crazy?
So that means you're ruining my new dish
over something as trivial as a kiss?
"Trivial"?
Is that why you two ran away the next day?
That's so boring!
Isn't there anything interesting?
Honestly, it's more surprising
that nothing has happened until now.
If I were with my ex,
I'd be overwhelmed with regret
and become all sentimental.
I'd get wasted and jump at him.
I really must be crazy
to come here and tell you all this.
Hey, you're adults.
Plus, you two used to date.
Things like that can happen
when the mood is right.
Everyone does that. What's the problem?
Not everyone is like you.
Not everyone is like you, either.
Just say, "Oh, it was a mistake"
and forget about it.
It's not that simple.
You always seem to complicate things.
Why are you sulking? What's the problem?
He hasn't called me since then
after he did something like that.
Hey, what are your fingers for?
You call him.
Or maybe he's already made up his mind.
He's decided to go,
"Sorry. It was a mistake."
He's not the type to do that.
What are you on about?
Do you still think he's your boyfriend?
You don't know anything.
He might seem dim-witted on the outside,
but he's actually much more
prudent than I am.
Jeez. Don't you get it?
If he wanted to get back together,
he would have come to you already.
But he…
Do you…
want to get back with him?
Are you worried that Ung might say
that it was all a mistake?
Don't tell me you still…
Yeon-su.
Since when?
From when you met him again?
Even on that day when I went to
see him again for the first time
since I had brutally dumped him…
Who…
…I was confident.
I just had to keep a hold of myself.
How have you been?
Answer me.
I just had to hide my feelings.
But…
What do I do, Sol-i?
I'm not confident anymore.
Yes. I'm eating something disgusting.
Why are you just standing there
with the lights off?
Your other room was squeaky clean too.
At least you seem to be cleaning properly.
I'll be staying here for a while.
Do whatever you want.
Like you always have.
I was in a good mood today.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
This is a disaster.
I'm done thinking.
I've reached a conclusion.
What are you doing?
Yeon-su.
Have you been drinking?
- Are you a douchebag?
- What?
You've really changed.
I don't care what you've been up to
or how free you had been all this time.
- But…
- Do you want some water?
After what you've done,
how can you pretend
as if nothing's happened?
Is that what people do these days?
Do they just kiss
and hold hands with anyone
and pretend it didn't happen?
You don't have to yell.
Since when did that become acceptable?
That's just being a douchebag.
Are you done?
How are you acting
as if nothing's happened?
Did you really have
nothing to say to me this whole time?
Really?
Should I apologize…
and say it was a mistake?
What?
Is that what you want?
But I don't want to.
Then what?
Then what do you want to do?
I'm not dating you again.
This is the conclusion I came to.
I see.
So you don't want to say that
it was a mistake and apologize
or start dating me again.
You just want me to get lost.
You should have told me faster
instead of dragging this out.
Despite what happened,
I can't go on without her in my life.
- Yeon-su.
- Don't call me.
I'm never going to
see you again, you jerk.
Should we be friends?
Let's be friends.
What?
You want us to be what?
Friends.
Why?
We've never tried being friends before.
Who knows?
We could be good friends.
Have you been drinking?
It's you who's been drinking.
- Or are you on your medication?
- Not yet. I'm taking them later.
Can you really be friends with me?
Yes.
Fine.
Let's be friends, then.
This is going to be fun.
Do you have anything else…
Can I stay over?
What?
We're friends, so that's okay, right?
Is this because you're drunk?
I'm doing this because we're friends.
- Hey.
- Where's your blanket?
You're not making a friend
sleep without a blanket, right?
Yeon-su!
You don't have to yell.
Jeez.
As you can see, I drank quite a lot.
I'm really tired, so can you be quiet?
Just go sleep on the bed then.
I'm going to be working downstairs.
No way. We're just friends,
so let's keep it that way.
And get me a blanket.
What is she thinking?
KIM JI-UNG
The person you have called…
That's an enthusiastic greeting.
What are you still doing here?
I took a shower.
Can I borrow your clothes?
I need some fresh clothes.
Just go home then.
- Why? Can't I stay?
- Why would you?
Because I want to hang out with my friend.
What's the problem?
Come on. Why are you doing this?
You know I don't have friends.
I'm excited that I've made a new friend
for the first time in 29 years.
Feel free to tell me
if you want to stop being friends.
I'll take some clothes from your closet.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Are you going to sleep now?
I'm going to.
Go to bed then. I'll just hang out here.
I hope you're gone by the time I'm up.
I'll decide that for myself, friend.
Get some sleep.
Unbelievable.
Jeez, what's wrong with her?
Wait.
How did she know I didn't get any sleep?
Good work.
Did you get some sleep on the plane?
What day is it today?
- It's Sunday, right?
- It's Saturday.
What? It isn't Sunday?
What are you doing on Sunday?
Why do you keep asking?
My schedule's empty on Sunday, right?
Yes, I told you.
- I'm going on a date.
- You don't mean…
- That artist?
- Yes.
Are you sure it's a date?
It's a date
if a man and a woman meet alone.
And we set up a date properly this time.
All right.
Just please don't cause any trouble.
Be careful.
I haven't caused any trouble these days.
Don't worry.
Wait, he'll be asleep.
- I'll call him later.
- Hang on.
Were you actually
being considerate just now?
Hey, you're right.
I didn't know I could do that.
I've changed.
Eat up before you go.
Ung.
How can your repertoire
be exactly the same every time?
That's actually incredible.
At least have one bite.
We can talk while you eat.
You always come and go whenever you want.
You don't have to try to act
like a mother to me in between.
You're still here?
Hey, you're up.
You slept less than expected.
You could die early at this rate.
Hey, that shirt…
Oh, this? I found it in your closet.
You didn't throw it away.
I didn't know it was there.
Really? It was folded up neatly though.
Do you feel awkward that I'm wearing
the matching shirt we wore as a couple
when we're friends now?
Gosh. Not at all. Do whatever you want.
Fine.
There were a lot of side dishes
in the fridge, so I made some stew.
- Do you want some?
- Hey.
This is my house,
and that's my food you're eating.
What should we do after we eat?
Do you want to play video games?
Aren't you going to go home?
Why? Can't I stay longer? We're friends--
You keep emphasizing the word "friend."
Why is that?
But you really want us
to be friends, right?
- Yes.
- Right. That's why.
So let me hang out here today.
That's okay, right?
All right, fine. Let's hang out all day.
What is it?
You have an interview today, remember?
- I'll pick you up at two.
- Right.
Cancel the interview for me.
What? Why?
I'm still not feeling that good.
Are you still sick?
I heard your fever went down.
Then I'll come over later.
No, don't come. I'm going to sleep. Bye.
Listen.
Luckily, I don't have any plans today.
So I'll hang out with you.
Okay, friend.
Do you want some?
I'll get it myself.
Ji-ung. Didn't you go home yesterday?
Why are you here on a weekend?
I was helping Mr. Park with a program.
Why would they do that
without asking me first?
Don't. I'll go talk to him.
It's nothing. I'll be done soon.
By the way, I notified everyone
that we're filming on Monday.
And I got a strange call a while ago.
What do you mean?
I don't know if it's true, but…
What is it?
NJ wants to appear on our program.
What? Who told you that?
NJ herself.
Appear as what?
As Choi Ung's friend.
This is so stressful.
Is this my third or my fourth win?
Why are you so good at this game?
Well, it'll be harder to find
something I'm not good at.
You're so annoying.
You should be reflecting on why you lost
instead of blaming others.
Video games require brains too.
Let's play just one more game.
Let's make a bet then.
If I keep going,
I'll just be doing you a favor.
What should we bet then?
One of your drawings.
Do you even know how much they cost?
- You can try to beat me then.
- Jeez.
All right, hang on. Let me get more juice.
Aren't you going to answer your phone?
I bet it's Eun-ho.
NJ
I guess you're quite close to her.
- Who?
- That famous singer.
NJ.
Just a bit.
It seems you keep in touch with her,
and she visits you often
despite her busy schedule.
Is there something going on
between you two?
What?
Why are you startled? Is there?
I mean, I was startled you asked that.
Friends can ask things like that.
I guess you can since we're friends.
Then let me ask you this.
What was going on
between you and Mr. Jang?
- What?
- I can ask that since we're friends.
We just know each other through work.
The others didn't seem to think that.
What do you mean?
And since we're on the topic,
since when were you so close to Ji-ung?
Really?
You two were never that close.
Are you being jealous right now?
- Yes.
- What?
What?
What I'm saying is
don't steal Ji-ung away from me.
He's my friend.
NJ
Sol-i.
If you take another step,
I won't let you leave.
You have to help me with this.
- I was just passing by.
- You come here every day.
I know, right?
This place is pretty charming.
The owner here is even more charming.
Don't like me.
I don't date younger guys.
Really? Thank you.
You have to keep your word!
Hey, why don't you come in for a minute?
No, I'm not going to help you.
That's not why I want you inside.
Come on in.
- No, I have to go.
- Where are you going?
Hey. Stop bumming around and work.
I had work today,
but Ung suddenly canceled.
He said he's still sick,
so I'm going to check in on him.
He's sick?
Yes. I'm I heard he was all better,
but he says he's sick again.
And he told me not to come.
But, as his manager,
I should go check in on him.
No, you shouldn't go.
Why?
- I'm sure he has a guest.
- A guest? Who?
Never mind. Anyway, you shouldn't go.
Just come here.
- Come on.
- No.
You promised not to do that.
I'm off-limits.
You're such a little brat.
Come over here
before I shower you with scallions.
- Are you leaving?
- Yes. Aren't you?
I'm going to work a little more. Go on.
All right.
Do you have something to say?
Ji-ung, well…
Do you want to join me for dinner?
You have to eat
if you're going to keep working,
and I don't have much to eat at home.
Sure.
Why are you explaining yourself?
Let's go eat.
We could have eaten out.
It's fine. You have to get back to work.
Fine, then.
Stop staring at me and spit it out.
Well, it's…
Are you having a rough time?
Do you want to be transferred
to a different team? Or quit?
I won't let you quit before I do.
You'd better get in line.
It's not that.
Then what is it?
Why do you keep staring at me?
Do you like Ms. Kook, Ji-ung?
Oh, I'm sorry.
That was too personal.
It just slipped out.
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry…
keep this a secret.
I haven't told anyone yet.
Was I that obvious?
I don't want anyone to know.
No, I only noticed
because I watched you carefully.
You should be focused on work.
That won't do.
- It's pretty low, right?
- What?
I'm deceiving my friend
and liking her in secret.
You can't control how you feel.
Are you taking my side?
I guess it's nice to have a junior.
Don't worry.
I'll finish this project without
getting my personal feelings involved.
- I'm ordering chicken!
- What?
I'm going to order chicken.
You're leaving?
I shouldn't spy on other people's phones.
But…
I can't help it
if I accidentally end up seeing it.
It's not like I'm blind.
GU EUN-HO
Ung, I rescheduled
today's interview to next week.
Are you still feeling sick?
And are you sure I don't have to come?
He said he had no plans.
What in the world is he thinking?
Did she really leave?
I don't want to go home.
I never said
you could snoop around my house.
You can't do whatever you want
because we're friends.
What's your plan?
What?
You were waiting for me to come back
so you could spray salt and water on me.
You agreed to do the documentary
just so that you can bully me,
hide from me, and reappear.
Then you kissed me.
And now you want to be friends?
I have no idea what you're thinking
so I want to find out.
I don't have any plans.
I just want us to get along as friends.
What's the problem?
But…
why do I feel like you're lying?
You're so conceited.
I have something I want to hear from you.
Come to think of it,
you never said it to me.
So I want to hear you say it now.
You can keep pretending we're friends.
I'm going to make plans of my own.
Oh, and…
I'm taking this since I won the bet.
Isn't this the amusement park
where we broke up for the fourth time?
I can have this, right?
Just leave.
I'm not letting you stay over tonight.
"Tonight"? Then can I come again
some other night?
You're being so weird. Do you know that?
I was about to go anyway.
After I eat the chicken.
Is it fried chicken?
Hang on!
What are you doing here at this hour?
What are you two doing?
Hello. I'm Choi Ung's friend, NJ…
EPILOGUE
Can I use a fake name?
The company doesn't know I'm doing this.
Can you blur my face? No, wait.
Will that make me look like a criminal?
Let's just start filming.
What do you want to know?
Should I talk about Choi Ung?
This is going to be fun.
But what's going on between you three?
It looks like you three got into a fight.
JUST FRIENDS
What are they up to?
- I like it.
- What?
You're not after some criminal.
You have a crush on him.
Hey, Ung!
Yeon-su.
Wait. Do you want to come up?
I don't want to be friends with Ung.
This is bad.
I guess I was wrong.
I do have a crush on him.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park